Finding Aid for the Edwin Wendell Pauley Papers, 1907-2001
UCLA Library, Department of Special Collections
- Photographs
  - EWP and Bobbe's 25th Wedding Anniversary (Box 13, Folder 9)
  - Tulin Airfield, Vienna (Box 13, Folder 10)
  - Cal Tech Jet Propulsion Laboratory (Box 13, Folder 11)
  - Northern Korea (Box 13, Folder 12)
  - Jimmy Mc Hugh Certificate of Merit reception - W.D.C. (Box 13, Folder 13)
  - Hunting Trip (Box 13, Folder 14)
    Includes signed photograph from Lucian C. Sprague and "Duck Netting in the Imperial Preserve" booklet
  - Presidential dinner party (Box 13, Folder 15)
  - EWP with Dwight E. Eisenhower, Kenneth G. Royall, William Draper, W. Stuart Symington, and J. Lawton Collins (Box 13, Folder 16)
  - Rabon Grande (Box 13, Folder 17)
  - Anheuser Busch Optimist Luncheon (Box 13, Folder 18)
  - Frances McKing? (Box 13, Folder 19)
  - EWP at Versailles, Hotel del Prado in Mexico (Box 13, Folder 20)
  - Egypt (Box 13, Folder 21)
  - EWP on horseback (Box 13, Folder 22)
  - Airplane and interior (Box 13, Folder 23)
  - Irving Stone Reception - "There Was Light" (Box 13, Folder 24)
  - Woodward Academy - EWP's grade school? in Alabama (Box 13, Folder 25)
  - Mexico City - Western Airlines (Box 14, Folder 1)
  - EWP with Rose Kohr (Miss Marina) and Governor Culbert L. Olson (Box 14, Folder 2)
  - EWP and Bobbe Pauley (Box 14, Folder 3)
  - EWP and Bobbe parasailing in Acapulco (Box 14, Folder 4)
  - EWP with General Larsen and Mr. Gates at Suribachi, Iwo Jima (Box 14, Folder 5)
  - Last picture of EWP with Bobbe, Mary Lou and Fred Maison (Box 14, Folder 6)
  - EWP and Bobbe asleep aboard plane (Box 14, Folder 7)
  - EWP watching Japanese chef prepare Sukiyaki duck (Box 14, Folder 8)
  - EWP and Bobbe's 30th Wedding Anniversary (Box 14, Folder 9)
    Includes invitation
  - EWP with Radio Executives - Robert Dick, Roy Turner, Henry Putnam, Ralph Fitkin, J. Howard Worrall, and M. H. Mulroney (Box 14, Folder 10)
  - EWP and Bobbe with Renee and Kay (Box 14, Folder 11)
  - EWP with Bill Heidman (Box 14, Folder 12)
  - EWP with award from Boy Scouts of America for distinguished service to boyhood (Box 14, Folder 13)
  - EWP with Nancy and Ronald Reagan (Box 14, Folder 14)
  - EWP at Rose Bowl game - bus departure announcement (Box 14, Folder 15)
  - Duck shot - Japan, film negative (Box 14, Folder 16)
  - EWP and Bobbe with swordfish in Acapulco, Mexico postcard (Box 14, Folder 17)
  - Bobbe Pauley with Mrs. Claude L. Cameron and Mrs. Homer Ferguson as Congressional spectators (Box 14, Folder 18)
  - Democratic Dinner (Box 14, Folder 19)
  - EWP with Bobbe and Courtrights (Box 14, Folder 20)
  - Tasha and Andy Pauley Baum wedding pictures (Box 14, Folder 21)
    Holiday card and paper printout
  - Harry S. Truman with children (Box 14, Folder 22)
  - Bobbe at Truman-Morse Dinner (Box 14, Folder 23)
    Includes letter from Del dated Dec 16, 1961
  - Bobbe Pauley (Box 14, Folder 24)
    Inscribed "With very best wishes to Edwin. Fondly 'Bobbe'"
  - EWP with two men at Hotel del Prado in Mexico (Box 14, Folder 25)
  - EWP with horse and cowboy (Box 14, Folder 26)
  - EWP and the Alabama Club (Box 14, Folder 27)
  - Miscellaneous portraits of EWP and Bobbe (Box 14, Folder 28)
  - EWP with Franklin Murphy and two unidentified men looking at the human brain (Box 14, Folder 29)
  - EWP with Clark Kerr and an unidentified man at a graduation ceremony (Box 14, Folder 30)
  - EWP with Franklin Murphy and two unidentified men at a graduation ceremony (Box 14, Folder 31)
  - Dean Rusk (Secretary of State under JFK) at a graduation ceremony (Box 14, Folder 32)
  - Clark Kerr and Prince Philip at a graduation ceremony (Box 14, Folder 33)
  - EWP in procession at a graduation ceremony (Box 14, Folder 34)
  - EWP with Tom Bradley (Box 14, Folder 35)
  - EWP with Arthur Rubinstein (Box 14, Folder 36)
    Signed by Arthur Rubinstein for EWP
  - EWP with Charles E. Young (Box 14, Folder 37)
  - Will Rogers (Box 14, Folder 38)
  - Miscellaneous photographs of machinery (Box 14, Folder 39)
  - EWP with unidentified men in western attire (Box 14, Folder 40)
  - EWP being sworn in (Box 14, Folder 41)
  - UC Regents (Box 14, Folder 42)
  - EWP and Bobbe with two unidentified men - award given to EWP from the County of Los Angeles (Box 14, Folder 43)
  - Miscellaneous photographs of ship's interior (Box 14, Folder 44)
  - Ship being engulfed by a wave (Box 14, Folder 45)
  - Miscellaneous family pictures (Box 14, Folder 46)
    One photograph dated Nov 1959
  - Miscellaneous group pictures of EWP with friends (Box 14, Folder 47)
  - Photographs of man with glass in hand (Box 14, Folder 48)
    Captioned "An oil man? Hell no, brother, I make my money with a football team"
  - EWP reading a newspaper (Box 14, Folder 49)
    Framed
  - EWP in cap and jacket in a field (Box 14, Folder 50)
  - EWP in graduation ceremony gown (Box 14, Folder 51)
    Black and white
  - EWP (Box 14, Folder 52)
  - EWP in a suit and striped tie (Box 14, Folder 53)
    Black and white; Includes one photograph signed by EWP to Bill Pagen
  - Sketched portrait of EWP (Box 14, Folder 54)
  - EWP in suit and tie taken by the Edward S. Curtis Studios (Box 14, Folder 55)
  - EWP in suit and tie taken by Blackstone Studios (Box 14, Folder 56)
  - Unfinished proofs of EWP (Box 14, Folder 57)
  - EWP, UC Board of Regents portrait (Box 14, Folder 58)
  - EWP in suit and tie taken by Vic Stein and Associates (Box 14, Folder 59)
    Black and white; Proofs
  - EWP sitting at desk with pen in hand (Box 14, Folder 60)
  - EWP in suit and tie taken by Vic Stein and Associates (Box 15, Folder 1)
  - EWP in suit and tie, sitting in chair (Box 15, Folder 2)
  - EWP in suit and tie taken by McNeill, McCleery, and Cochran (Box 15, Folder 3)
    Black and white; Includes bio about EWP
  - EWP in suit and tie (Box 15, Folder 4)
  - EWP in suit and tie by CJ Fox (Box 15, Folder 5)
    Glossy finish, same portrait as box 18, folder 4
  - EWP in suit and tie by CJ Fox (Box 15, Folder 6)
    Linen finish, same portrait as box 18, folder 4
  - EWP in suit, tie, and hat by Harris and Ewing (Box 15, Folder 7)
  - EWP in suit and tie by Harris and Ewing (Box 15, Folder 8)
  - EWP in suit and tie by Harris and Ewing (Box 15, Folder 9)
    Black and white; Glossy finish
  - Miscellaneous color photographs of family and friends (Box 15, Folder 10)
  - Miscellaneous black and white photographs of family and friends (Box 15, Folder 11)
  - EWP with Susie and Bobbe with Susie (Box 15, Folder 13)
    Metal frame with engraving
  - Bono Batani (Box 15, Folder 14)
  - EWP with Hubert Humphrey (Box 16, Folder 1)
  - EWP with Sam Yorty (Box 16, Folder 2)
  - EWP with S.H. Johnson (Box 16, Folder 3)
  - Harold Ickes (Box 16, Folder 4)
  - EWP and Bobbe (Box 16, Folder 5)
  - Coconut Island (Box 16, Folder 6)
  - Coconut Island (Box 16, Folder 7)
  - EWP and Dan Reeves (Box 16, Folder 13)
  - Ellen Van Patten - EWP's mother and wife of Elbert Pauley (Box 17, Folder 2)
  - EWP with Lyndon B. Johnson (Box 17, Folder 3)
  - EWP with Vice President of Vietnam Nguyen Cao Ky (Box 17, Folder 4)
    Includes correspondence from Colonel Dao-Huy-Ngoc, Chief Secretary to the Vice President (April 23, 1971) and J. Patrick Garner's business card
  - Lyndon B. Johnson (Box 17, Folder 5)
  - EWP with Lyndon B. Johnson (Box 17, Folder 6)
  - EWP with JFK (Box 17, Folder 7)
  - Bobbe with Vice President Humphrey (Box 17, Folder 8)
    Includes correspondence from Christy Fox
  - EWP and Bobbe at the World Affairs Council Reception (Box 17, Folder 9)
  - EWP with Nikita Kruschev (Box 17, Folder 10)
  - Bobbe with family and friends (Box 17, Folder 11)
  - Henry Wallace (Box 17, Folder 14)
  - EWP with unidentified man (Box 17, Folder 15)
  - EWP with Bobbe, Rick Hellyer, daughter Susan, secretary Sage Bjornsen, daughter in law Marylyn, Monager Admiral Heath, and son Buzz and Stephen Pauley (Box 17, Folder 16)
  - EWP and unidentified woman with swordfish (Box 17, Folder 17)
  - Jackson Day Dinner (Box 18, Folder 1)
  - Democratic National Finance Committee Luncheon (Box 18, Folder 1)
  - EWP with Bobbe and friends on the old pier on Coconut Island (Box 18, Folder 1)
  - Democratic National Committee Meeting - Palmer House - Chicago (Box 18, Folder 1)
  - Panoramic portrait of the Edwin W. Pauley Track at University of California, Santa Barbara (Box 18, Folder 1)
  - Los Angeles landscape (Box 18, Folder 1)
    Oversized; 2 different views
  - Pauley Mission Around the World (Box 18, Folder 2)
    Oversized; One colored, one black and white
  - Atomic Bomb Test - Los Alanios (Box 18, Folder 3)
  - EWP with JFK and Jacqueline Kennedy (Box 19, Folder 1)
  - EWP (Box 19, Folder 2)
    Oversized; Copy of photograph with signature below picture
  - EWP (Box 19, Folder 3)
    Oversized; Label to Gerard Waller
  - EWP with Bobbe, Bob Hope, Shah and Empress of Iran (Box 19, Folder 4)
  - EWP with Lyndon B. Johnson at graduation ceremony (Box 19, Folder 5)
  - EWP with King Hussein of Jordan (Box 19, Folder 6)
  - EWP with King Philip at graduation ceremony (Box 19, Folder 7)
  - Reception for VP Richard Nixon at the Pauley Home (Box 19, Folder 8)
    Oversized; Includes Correspondence
  - EWP with Lyndon B. Johnson (Box 19, Folder 9)
  - Kenneth Clairborne Royall? (Box 19, Folder 10)
  - University of California, Berkeley (football stadium) - honoring JFK (Box 19, Folder 11)
  - George Bush and Michael Dukakis at the Presidential Debate (Box 19, Folder 13)
    Oversized; Framed, Presented to the Pauley Foundation
  - Pat and Bernice Brown (Box 20, Folder 1)
  - Bobbe and other ladies at the Eve Awards (Box 20, Folder 2)
  - EWP and Bobbe with friends at their house party (Box 20, Folder 3)
  - EWP with Bobbe, General and Mrs. Mark Clark on Coconut Island (Box 20, Folder 4)
  - EWP (Box 20, Folder 5)
    Oversized; Taken by Conway Studios
  - Ernest Orlando Lawrence (Box 20, Folder 6)
  - Unknown - Uncle Carl Schwarzkopf??? (Box 20, Folder 7)
  - EWP with Madame Chiang Kai Shek (Box 20, Folder 8)
  - Chester W. Nimitz (Box 20, Folder 9)
  - Lyndon B. Johnson (Box 20, Folder 10)
    Oversized; Taken by Arnold Newman
  - EWP with General Mark Clark and navy men; Unidentified Naval officer with unidentified man (Box 20, Folder 11)
  - Bobbe with Stephen and Susan Pauley (Box 20, Folder 12)
  - EWP with 2 unidentified men at the bar on Coconut Island (Box 20, Folder 13)
  - EWP with Monager Admiral Heath and secretary Sage Bjornsen (Box 20, Folder 14)
  - Ernest Lawrence taken by A. Jonnaiux (Box 20, Folder 15)
    Oversized; Inscribed by Ernest Lawrence and A. Jonnaiux
  - Pauley staff on beach (Box 20, Folder 16)
  - EWP and family (Box 20, Folder 17)
  - Dinley Mundersoy (Box 20, Folder 18)
  - Leon Henderson (Box 20, Folder 19)
    Oversized; Holograph: To Ed Pauley- in recognition of bravery - Leon Henderson
  - [Edwin Pauley Jr.] (Box 20, Folder 20)
    Oversized; 2 Drawings by Russell Iredell; Large: 34.5 cm (h) x 27 cm (w), small: 24.7 cm (h) x 19.4 cm (w)
  - Edwin Pauley in black suit and tie, sitting with cigarette in hand (Box 20, Folder 21)
  - Map of North Atlantic Ocean and USS John F. Kennedy (Bill Pagen) (Box 20, Folder 22)
    Oversized; Signed by various officers on board
  - EWP (Box 20, Folder 23)
    Oversized; 7 different poses taken by Paul Hesse
  - Photograph of painting of EWP and miscellaneous petroleum machinery (Box 20, Folder 24)
    Oversized; By Bailey
  - Black and White portrait of EWP inscribed for Bill Pagen (Box 21, Folder 1)
    Oversized; 4 copies
  - EWP with Susan Jean Pauley and Stephen Pauley (Box 21, Folder 3)
  - Bobbe, Susan Jean in arm, Steve in baby cradle (Box 21, Folder 4)
    Oversized; Taken by Lansdowne; 2 copies
  - EWP, Bobbe, daughter, sons, and Marie McHenry at Christmas (Box 21, Folder 5)
    Oversized; Taken by Ray Huff
  - EWP, Bobbe, daughter, and sons at Christmas (Box 21, Folder 6)
    Oversized; Taken by Charles Kirbe
  - Aerial view of unidentified topography (Bill Pagen) (Box 21, Folder 8)
    Oversized; Two copies; Labeled as USS John F. Kennedy (CV 67)
  - Susan Jean Pauley? (Box 21, Folder 9)
    Oversized; Taken by Harris and Ewing
  - EWP and friend on beach chair on Coconut Island (Box 21, Folder 10)
  - EWP in suit and tie facing right (Box 21, Folder 11)
  - EWP in suit and tie facing front (Box 21, Folder 12)
  - EWP in suit, tie, and hat facing left (Box 21, Folder 13)
  - EWP in tweed suit and tie (Box 21, Folder 14)
  - EWP in tweed suit and tie with Edwin Pauley Jr.? on bike (Box 21, Folder 15)
  - Dinner dance for Vice President Humphrey (Box 22, Folder 1)
  - 25th Wedding anniversary (Box 22, Folder 2)
  - Landscape of Coconut Island - Harbor (Box 22, Folder 3)
    Oversized; Blue paper frame
  - Bobbe standing behind chair (Box 22, Folder 4)
    Oversized; Taken by Skipsey, black and white, 2 copies, paper framed
  - Bobbe sitting in chair with hands grasped (Box 22, Folder 5)
  - Bobbe standing at the bottom of the stairs in light blue dress (Box 22, Folder 6)
    Oversized; Taken by Curtis Studios, paper framed
  - Kaneohe Bay (Box 22, Folder 7)
  - Lyndon B. Johnson (Box 22, Folder 9)
    Oversized; Framed, addressed to Bobbe, in tarnished frame, bottom part of photo damaged
  - Miscellaneous duplicates (Box 27, Folder 3)
  - Autopositive and Print of Modesto Bee (Box 44, Folder 4)
    Oversized; In tube
  - EWP with unknown men in suits (Box 45, Folder 8)
  - Pauley Petroleum Inc. (Box 45, Folder 12)
  - Party for President Truman (Box 52, Folder 7)
  - Regent and Mrs. John Canady-Cunningham, and Marge Wookman leaving Coconut Island on the Ramona (Box 59, Folder 10)
  - Thomas MacBride with head Coconut Island cook, Rose (Box 59, Folder 11)
  - EWP and Bobbe with Edith Ayres, Admiral Soloman, Marnella Miranda, Marge Woolman, Secretary Board of Regents?, John Lawrence, and children water skiing (Box 59, Folder 12)
  - EWP and Bobbe with John Lawrence and daughter, Tom and Ruth Cunningham, Marge Woolman, and Herb Childs on Coconut Island pier (Box 59, Folder 13)
  - EWP with "Andy Fix" (Andy Anderon) (Box 59, Folder 14)
  - Part of the old Marine Lab at Coconut Island (Box 59, Folder 15)
  - EWP with Arthur Ayres and Dr. John Lawrence (Box 59, Folder 16)
  - Tea honoring Bobbe by Chancellor Charles Young and Sue (Box 60, Folder 28)
  - Bobbe speaking at Board of Trustees, UCLA Foundation dinner? (Box 60, Folder 29)
  - Bobbe in bed with cat, dog, and Bobbe ready for Masquerade ball (Box 60, Folder 30)
  - Renovation of backyard (Box 60, Folder 31)
  - Bobbe's trip to the pier and Bobbe's cat (Box 60, Folder 32)
  - Bobbe birthday dinner at Trader Vic's (Box 60, Folder 33)
    Negatives only
  - Baby Cat, car after accident?, and Mentryville (Box 60, Folder 34)
  - Bobbe's boating trip and miscellaneous pictures from the sky (Box 60, Folder 35)
  - Bobbe with birthday balloons, present, and cake (Box 60, Folder 36)
  - Bobbe's graduation (Box 61, Folder 2)
  - Bobbe at reopening of Angel's Flight (Box 61, Folder 3)
  - Bobbe with George Page at Hammer dinner at Perinos (Box 61, Folder 8)
  - Bobbe with resident quartet (Box 61, Folder 9)
  - Bobbe with Annie and Tanya at Forest Lawn after Ora's burial at Carmel (Box 61, Folder 10)
  - Bobbe at christening of Bobbe Jean (Box 61, Folder 11)
  - Georgia Military Academy (Box 61, Folder 12)
    Includes News Clippings
  - Bobbe - for magazine spread? (Box 61, Folder 13)
  - Various photographs of Bobbe (Box 61, Folder 14)
  - Bobbe with family and friends - miscellaneous (Box 61, Folder 15)
    Includes negatives. With clipped articles from magazines.
  - Miscellaneous Photographs of Bobbe, Bill, Family and Friends (Box 98, Folder 11)
  - Rochester Corporation - Culpepper, Virginia (Box 99, Folder 7)
  - Bobbe and Bill (Box 99, Folder 9)
    In silver frame with engraving
  - EWP (Box 114, Folder 3)
    Oversized; Taken by Gladser Studios
  - EWP (Box 114, Folder 4)
    Oversized; Unfinished Proof
  - Alabama Class 1918-1919 (Box 114, Folder 6)
  - Cinosam Class A. and A.S.R. Valley of Pasadena (Box 114, Folder 7)
  - Harold Pauley and EWP as a child (Box 120, Folder 1)
  - Coconut Island Slides (Box 120, Folder 3)
    Includes identifying list
  - Coconut Island Slides (Box 120, Folder 4)
  - Coconut Island Slides (Box 120, Folder 5)
  - Coconut Island Slides (Box 120, Folder 6)
  - Coconut Island Slides (Box 120, Folder 7)
  - Coconut Island Slides (Box 120, Folder 8)
    Duplicates
  - Coconut Island Slides (Box 120, Folder 9)
  - Miscellaneous - Lurline and sports (Box 120, Folder 10)
  - Ski Trip (Box 120, Folder 11)
  - Mexico Trip (Box 120, Folder 12)
  - Hawaii (Box 120, Folder 13)
    Stereo Slides
  - Miscellaneous Large Negatives (Box 120, Folder 14)
  - Hi-speed daylight Minox asa 32 color film (Box 120, Folder 15)
  - EWP, Bobbe, and family on Hawaii Trip (Box 120, Folder 16)
    Large Negative
  - EWP, Bobbe, and family in front of Christmas tree (Box 122, Folder 2)
  - EWP, Bobbe, with Christine and Ed Carter in costumes at home of E.L. Cord (Box 122, Folder 9)
  - EWP and Bobbe (Box 122, Folder 10)
    Oversized; Taken by Harris Ewing
  - EWP taken by Paul Hesse (Box 122, Folder 11)
  - "To Ed from Harold - Xmas - '47" (Box 128, Folder 1)
  - Miscellaneous EWP and family photos (Box 128, Folder 2)
  - Robert Pauley Black and White Wedding Photo Album (Box 128, Folder 3)
  - Coastal Oil Rigs in many different views and angles (Box 136, Folder 1)
  - Coconut Island
    - Sports-Skiing, Skiers on Mauna Kea, Island of Hawaii (Box 5, Folder 2)
    - Caption line - Honolulu's Collection of Customs (Box 5, Folder 3)
    - Cut line - A Boy Male Threesome (Box 5, Folder 4)
    - Caption line - Don Beach-Comber (Box 5, Folder 5)
    - Coconut Island Club (Box 5, Folder 7)
    - Welton Becket, Mayor San Yorty, Mrs. Yorty, and Dr. Jack French (Box 5, Folder 8)
    - Allen Chase (Box 5, Folder 9)
    - EWP with "Red" Skelton (Box 5, Folder 10)
    - EWP and Bobbe Pauley at the Edwin W. Pauley Marine Laboratory (Box 5, Folder 11)
    - Mother - Marie McHenry (Box 5, Folder 12)
    - Shower Tree (Box 5, Folder 13)
    - New passenger boat (Box 5, Folder 14)
    - New Marine Laboratory (Box 5, Folder 15)
    - Bobbe and Buzz Pauley (Box 5, Folder 16)
    - Birthday and Bobbe - Ed, red-dress, ducks, Ora and John leasing - film negatives (Box 5, Folder 17)
    - EWP, family and friends - helicopter ride and miscellaneous photographs (Box 5, Folder 18)
    - Carters, Browns, turtles, everyone - film negatives (Box 5, Folder 19)
    - EWP and Bobbe Pauley (Box 5, Folder 20)
    - EWP on Coconut Island (Box 5, Folder 21)
    - Bronze plaque honoring outstanding alumni for Woodward Academy (Box 5, Folder 22)
      Includes correspondence from M.C. Paget, Director of Development and Alumni Affairs
    - Miscellaneous film negatives (Box 5, Folder 23)
    - Miscellaneous slides (Box 5, Folder 24)
    - Landscape photographs (Box 6, Folder 1)
    - Miscellaneous black and white photographs of family and friends on Coconut Island and landscape of Coconut Island (Box 6, Folder 2)
    - Miscellaneous color photographs of family and friends on Coconut Island and landscape of Coconut Island (Box 6, Folder 3)
      Includes film negatives for one set of photographs
    - Landscape of Maui (Box 7, Folder 31)
    - Rosemary Wilson Aloha Party and Bikinis (Box 7, Folder 32)
    - Bobbe, Cheadles, Williams, Kendalls - waving goodbye to Red Miller in dress whites (Box 7, Folder 33)
    - Christmas tree and Tasha on bike, dedication of beach house (Box 7, Folder 34)
    - Leaving Coconut Island - EWP and Bobbe (Box 7, Folder 35)
    - Bobbe (Box 7, Folder 36)
    - EWP, Bobbe, friends, and landscape photos of Coconut Island (Box 7, Folder 37)
    - EWP, Bobbe, Bob Kendalls, Meredith Williams (Box 7, Folder 38)
    - Miscellaneous film negatives (Box 7, Folder 39)
    - Black and white photographs of EWP, Bobbe, Red Skelton, Pat and Bernice Brown, family, friends, and landscape on Coconut Island (Box 8, Folder 1)
    - Miscellaneous color photographs (Box 8, Folder 2)
    - Polaroids of miscellaneous framed photographs and paintings (Box 8, Folder 3)
    - EWP with Harry S. Truman on boat (Box 8, Folder 4)
    - Dr. Kam's Party at Coconut Island (Box 8, Folder 5)
    - EWP, Bobbe, Marie McHenry, and Buzz on ship (Box 8, Folder 6)
    - Film negatives of EWP and family (Box 8, Folder 7)
    - Early pictures of Coconut Island (Box 8, Folder 8)
    - Landscape photographs of Coconut Island (Box 8, Folder 9)
    - EWP, Bobbe, and friends (Box 8, Folder 10)
    - EWP, Bobbe, Kendalls, Gaye, Cheadle - Japanese night, various views (Box 8, Folder 11)
    - Outrigger, Bobbe - legs (Box 8, Folder 12)
    - EWP and Bobbe with burro and dog (Box 8, Folder 13)
    - Landscape photographs after natural disaster (Box 8, Folder 14)
    - EWP and friends - Pali (Box 8, Folder 15)
    - Bobbe and Ora (Box 8, Folder 16)
    - Beach house (Box 8, Folder 17)
    - Bobbe, U.S. Air Force plane, and landscape photographs (Box 8, Folder 18)
    - Various views of island (Box 8, Folder 19)
    - Cheadles, Aloha - Brian, Kevin (Box 8, Folder 20)
    - Bobbe (Box 8, Folder 21)
    - Various views of island (Box 8, Folder 22)
    - Hawaii and Mojo interior (Box 8, Folder 23)
    - Bed and Breakfast - Kahala (Box 8, Folder 24)
    - Bobbe, Marge, Harry, and various views of island (Box 8, Folder 25)
    - Bobbe and various city views of island (Box 8, Folder 26)
    - Asphalt spill and Bobbe, Lambert et al, and Annie at party (Box 8, Folder 27)
    - Contractors Party - Bob, Ora, and Annie (Box 8, Folder 28)
    - Bobbe and Hawaii after natural disaster (Box 8, Folder 29)
    - Kahala, Plant, Lighthouse - Diamond Head (Box 9, Folder 1)
    - Coconut Island Contractor Party, Honolulu, Coconut Island from airplane (Box 9, Folder 2)
    - Bobbe and various views of island (Box 9, Folder 3)
    - Sea Life Park (Box 9, Folder 4)
    - Hurricane damage lanais, Haiku Gardens (Box 9, Folder 5)
    - Bobbe and friends - Japanese night and various views of island (Box 9, Folder 6)
    - Koshoggi helicopter shots (Box 9, Folder 7)
    - Bobbe, friends, and various views of island (Box 9, Folder 8)
    - Bobbe and friends at dinner party (Box 9, Folder 9)
    - Bobbe and friends at dinner party, boat trip, girls diving, and various views of island (Box 9, Folder 10)
    - Bobbe and friends at dinner party, Japanese night, and boat trip (Box 9, Folder 11)
    - Bobbe and friends at lunch party and boat trip (Box 9, Folder 12)
    - Bobbe, and friends, fishing trip (Box 9, Folder 13)
    - Coconut Island from Koshoggi helicopter (Box 9, Folder 14)
    - Shots of Coconut Island, Mary Lou and Fred (Box 9, Folder 15)
    - Bobbe and friends on boat trip (Box 9, Folder 16)
    - Bobbe and friends and various views of island (Box 9, Folder 17)
    - Bobbe and friends and various views of island (Box 9, Folder 18)
    - Kaneohe - ? Gardens (Box 9, Folder 19)
    - Sauce Bros., Honolulu - Kahala Hilton (Box 10, Folder 1)
    - Kahala Hilton - Coconut Island new lanais (Box 10, Folder 2)
    - Kahala Hilton (Box 10, Folder 3)
    - Kahala Hilton - porpoises (Box 10, Folder 4)
    - Film negatives of Bobbe, family, and friends on boating trip and various aerial views of island (Box 10, Folder 5)
    - Film negatives of Bobbe and friends at bike race? (Box 10, Folder 6)
    - Pauley Gardens (Box 10, Folder 7)
    - Party with Bobbe, J. Bardach, M. Hill, Mrs. Peter Char, Mrs. Wilke, P. Lang, Mrs. McNaughton, Spengler, D. Mackail, J. Wheelon, B. Williams, F. Wellborn, N. Walker (Box 10, Folder 8)
      Same party as box 13, f. 9 and f. 10
    - Party with Bobbe, U. Walker, P. Spaulding, N. Walker, J. Bardach, B. Williams, C. Johnson, Harriet and Charles Luckman, Kenda, McNaughton, Nancy Jackson? (Box 10, Folder 9)
      Same party as box 13, f. 8 and F. 10